Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Master Nobu.
The necessary preparations
have been made.
It's ready for use. should
it come to that.
And as per your
orders. we just obtained these.
Twenty targets in
total. all in New York City.
After
years of searching...
the fate of Black Sky is in our hands.
Now this Daredevil is the only
thing that stands in our way.
- I suggest you get to work.
- Which one would you like to hit?
All of them.
We need to lay low.
They're gonna come for us.
Bullshit. They'll come
for her. What is this?
I'm sorry. old man. but I just can't
take chances with you anymore.
You're naïve.
She should be tied
in this chair. not me.
She is not the problem. They are.
They're gonna turn this city upside down
looking for her. Matty.
They'll watch it burn.
That's why I said we
need to work together.
There is no together.
All these years. I tried to tame her.
I should have let her bleed
out in the back of that car.
You should have some damn
gratitude. She spared your life.
The Black Sky cannot be controlled.
manipulated or transported.
It must be extinguished at all costs.
You wanna talk about being naïve?
'Cause right now you're
tied to a chair...
spouting rhetoric about an ancient war.
Do you even have a plan?
I'm working on it.
Well. while you're working on it. son.
do me a favor
and pull your head out of your ass.
- The Black Sky...
- The Black Sky is bullshit. Stick.
It's a myth. No one believes it but you.
Every assassin in the Hand believes it.
What do you think they're
gonna do about it?
What about what I believe. Stick?
What about what I'm gonna do about it?
Leave me alone. Matthew.
Stick's downstairs.
He's restrained.
You know. whatever you're
feeling. it's gonna pass.
What do you know about what I'm feeling?
Just...
consider the possibility that
there is no such thing as a Black Sky.
That it's... it's mysticism.
you know? It's nonsense.
I've been trained
to kill it since I was a kid.
Yeah. maybe
everything they taught you was a lie.
Stick says I have a gift.
The special kind. the kind
very few people have...
"The kind very few
people have or deserve." I know.
I got the same speech.
Stick likes his
fortune-cookie wisdom. but...
that's all he needed. 'cause he was
training children to fight a war.
You can't deny it.
Some of what the Hand
does defies explanation.
Just because I don't
understand something
doesn't mean I'm ready to
chalk it up as some fairy tale.
True or not...
the legend says
that once they have the Black Sky
they'll be capable of anything.
It's not about what I'm willing to do.
Even in a cage I'll be their false idol.
They'll do terrible things in my name
because they think the Black
Sky will make them invincible.
Well. they can't have you.
You don't belong to anyone.
And you may be smarter and stronger
and more powerful than
anyone they've ever met...
but like I keep saying.
they don't get to tell you who you are.
Their organization is
older than most countries.
They're powerful...
and they're everywhere.
And they survived
just like the Chaste...
by staying in the shadows...
by getting people to believe wholeheartedly
in their legend.
But if we shine a light on
them. they'll scatter... all right?
We can take them down.
Not Stick's way. We can do it our way.
You would trust me...
after all I've put you through?
The Hand's ninjas can
mask their heartbeats...
Yours is always loud and clear.
I've been fighting
this war my whole life.
I've heard every story.
Some people say Nobu's
lived three lifetimes.
A criminal record
that goes back decades.
True or not. he's the head of the snake.
But he's our best
chance of taking down the Hand.
Then our job is simple. We
find Nobu. We extract him.
We remove him from the Hand
without alerting his troops.
Can't be that easy.
Giving up is easy.
You will kill him?
No.
That would make him a martyr.
I wanna dethrone him.
Defrock him and let him rot in a cell.
Show this cult of
his that their holy man...
isn't anything but a guy.
- We'll have to find him first.
- Yeah.
And I say we head straight
into the lion's den.
The last thing they're expecting
is that we hit back at them now.
You would risk everything for me?
So how do we do this?
Not alone.
We do it together.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
Our firm represents
Hell's Kitchen's top clients.
Of course. by accepting our offer
you'll get a personal
assistant. a corner office.
and the opportunity to branch out
and build your own client base.
Your former associate. Ms. Marci Stahl.
recommends you very highly.
And after reviewing the
infamous Punisher trial.
I would be foolish not to invite
a talent like yourself onto our team.
Hopefully. you'll find our
starting salary competitive.
That's...
one way to describe it.
It gets better.
How does "Hogarth. Chao. Benowitz
and Nelson" sound?
Like a mouthful.
A good mouthful.
You think outside of the box.
and that is exactly what
we're looking for.
If the past few months
are any indication.
my firm is going to need a
very resourceful attorney.
Someone like you...
who's not afraid to take on
riskier. non-traditional cases.
Cases involving vigilantes.
Let's call them "people
with complexities."
You have no idea.
Try me.
Yeah. I don't know about this.
I made all this
stuff to keep Betsy safe.
not just give it away.
- You'll get it back. Melvin.
- Without a scratch.
Promise.
If you say so.
Expecting trouble?
- Yeah. a little bit.
- That figures.
Well. it's a good thing you got company.
Ah. before I forget.
These are for you.
Merry Christmas. huh?
What is it?
Billy club.
Like the cops use. only.
like. a million times cooler.
It's my own design.
Special steel fiber composite cable.
Damn near indestructible.
Check it out. You can change the length.
Here. play with it.
- Where's mine?
- That's. uh...
- It's a prototype. I only made one.
- Hey. Hey. don't mind her.
So. check it out.
You could use it as a
grappling hook. or. uh...
close quarter combat.
The possibilities are endless. Here.
Melvin. I... I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
I mean. the papers might
not report it. but...
some of us in Hell's Kitchen.
we know who's really looking out for us.
It's yours. man.
How does it feel?
Knowing that the kids you've trained
are going to fight your war for you...
while you're sitting here?
Biggest mistake of your life. child.
Maybe.
But it'll be my
mistake. because this is my life.
All right. let's go.
We'll hit the tunnels and
we'll spread out from...
Foggy. Foggy. Foggy.
Foggy.
- Will you take that?
- Foggy.
- Yeah. I'll just be a sec.
Foggy?  Yeah.
Sorry. man. it's not a good time.
- I was afraid you'd say that.
- Are you at the police station?
Brett says he's in deep
shit and needs legal counsel.
so he was just
desperate enough to call me.
I figured it was my
problem till I got down here.
took a look at his face.
Something went down. He won't spill it.
but he's been roughed up. He
says it was some gangbangers.
But I've known him long
enough to tell when he's lying.
- Why does he need a lawyer?
- They wanted files. Matt.
Classified police stuff.
All right. this... It's
gonna have to wait. I can't...
Not just any files. They
were asking about you.
And I'm not talking about Matt Murdock.
- Uh. what did they want?
- I have no idea.
But from the looks of
him. they wanted it pretty bad.
He's helped us and Daredevil.
stuck his neck out
when he didn't have to.
- And now...
- Yeah. okay. I'm on it.
- I'll be right down.
- Okay.
You better be.
So... this is
what it's come to. huh?
The masked vigilante is
the only one I can trust.
What happened?
I knew it was just a matter of time
till you showed up... again.
It'd be better if you
just told me. Detective.
Not the first time some
asshole roughs me up.
The job... This shit ain't easy.
But then they said they
got eyes on my mom.
Said they were gonna kill her.
Even put her on the phone.
Who?
No idea. Worked
for someone big. though.
Had real power behind those
fists. and I'm not talking muscles.
They wanted everything we had on you.
I don't imagine you have much.
Well. it might surprise you to know that
we do keep track of
two things real well.
Records of people you put away...
and incident reports.
Records on everyone else.
Everyone else?
That's what they were after.
They wanted to know everyone
you ever saved.
Karen.
Get your damn
hands off me. asshole!
Hey.
Any idea who these people are?
No.
Where'd they grab you?
- Who gives a shit?
- Just tell me.
42nd and 9th.
Wasn't doing nothing. Taking
a goddamn stroll.
Supposed to be on house arrest.
House arrest?
You're being monitored?
- What are you. my PO?
- Look. I'm trying to help here.
Thank God.
That means they know you're here.
Mmm. I might have
tampered with it a bit.
- What?
- A boy's gotta get out once in a while.
- you know what I mean?
- Put it on. Turn it back on.
- And get shot by these assholes?
-  No more talking.
Do you want to stay alive or what?
- What's your name?
- Karen Page.
What's yours?
You leave her alone!
I was a POW in Laos. This is a cakewalk.
You and me!
One on one. Huh? Coward!
- Coward!
- Hey! Look. look. look. look. look!
He doesn't know what he's
saying. all right? He's scared.
Not anymore.
The next one to make a sound dies.
Hey.
Come on.
Come on. come on.
The people they took aren't the target.
They're bait. The Hand's
trying to lure me in.
It's me they want.
- You're the only thing in their way.
- Those people are innocent.
You can't just take the bait.
I know. but I can't just
abandon them either.
I know.
We gotta get ahead of this thing
before any of them get hurt.
Slow your breath.
Focus.
Okay. Focus.
You'll find them.
You'll find her. Matthew.
I can't hear... hear anything!
The electricity in this
building is too loud.
- The city is pulsing like...
- Matthew. it's... it's your city.
Calm it down.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Tune out everything
that's not essential.
Now...
one at a time.
Okay. go!
Shit.
Take care
of it. I'll tell him.
What part of house arrest
do these assholes not understand?
10-13. officer down. 36th and 7th.
They stuck him with a goddamn arrow!
Copy that. 10-13.
Officer down. Backup on the way. Over.
This is
it. There's police below.
Two officers already dead.
Fifteen. twenty hostages inside.
Nobu's men?
Yeah. they can hide their hearts. but...
when there's this many of them.
they're buzzing like a beehive.
- How many?
- I don't know.
Could be an army.
- Can you isolate Nobu?
- No.
We can't move until
we're sure he's here.
We have to do something before
these people get hurt.
I'm not here for them.
I came to take down
Nobu and you said you'd help.
I know. and I will. Elektra. but
right now. the people in that...
They were used to draw us out.
I'm sorry. Matthew. but
saving them wouldn't help us.
There are 20 innocent people in there.
If we go in there right
now. Nobu gets what he wants.
You dead. me captured. The Hand wins.
I know it's harsh.
but the people in
there are a drop in the ocean
compared to what happens
next if Nobu gets hold of me.
These people are in
danger because of me.
And I'll be damned if
I'm not getting them out.
- It's the wrong play.
- It's the only play.
You stay here. I got work to do.
It's gonna be fine.
- Shit.
-  No.
Please. oh. no. please. It's nothing!
There's nothing there.
You don't have to look.
It's a family heirloom. It's nothing.
It's okay. It's
fine.  No. Listen. calm down.
It's nothing.
There's a button. we can...
Hold on.
No. No! Get off me!
- It wasn't my idea!
- You don't have to do that! Please!
He'll turn it off! Oh. my God!
Out the door. take a right!
Go!
Go. go. go. go! Hurry!
Here.
You're okay?
Better now. Oh. God.
- Go. go. go.
- No. no. no... wait. wait. wait.
Keep going out the door.
Wait. you okay?
- Can you help her?
-  Yeah.
Okay. Come on.
I got bored.
The only way out is
up. Let's head to the roof.
The
Black Sky will be ours.
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire.
Sarge. they have snipers
on all the entrances. We can't go in.
Okay. well. hold your fire.
Somebody's coming out.
I said hold your fire.
Oh. shit.
Get EMS on scene now!
These people are in shock. Get
'em out of here and get 'em help.
- Move!
-  Brett?
- Page?
- Yeah.
Any shitstorm you're not a part
of? What's going on up there?
These people are being used for bait.
There's some kind
of weird cult up there.
and they want Daredevil.
We need those big lights!
Light it up! Hit 'em up
there. there. and there!
If something happens on
that roof. I wanna see it.
Karen!
Foggy? What are you doing here?
Jesus. Brett said there was shit
going down. but he didn't say this.
- Yeah.
- I'm just glad you're okay.
Thanks. But I'm not
the only one in danger.
What's going on up there?
I think it might be the
end of vigilantes in New York.
Holy shit.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
There's a lot more coming.
One thing's for sure.
We're gonna die.
Do you wanna end it
here... or on the roof?
I've always liked the fresh air.
What's up there?
Oh. Jesus.
Too many to count.
Armed. packing
katanas. couple of longbows.
More coming up from below. Same weapons.
I'd say we've got a couple of minutes
before they break through that door.
Okay.
Even if we survive...
we may not see each other again.
Okay. let's do it.
Wait. wait. Wait for
one second. One second.
So. what if...
What if...
from now on. if... if we make it...
wherever you run. I...
I run with you?
You're not serious.
I've never been more serious.
This... Elektra. this
is a part of me that I need.
And you're the only one who gets it.
Without this. I'm not
alive. I'm not. Not really.
And I know that now. thanks to you.
I don't know what we are together.
and if we have any
chance in the future...
I don't...
But I... I do know
that I'm free with you.
Like with no one else.
You hide from yourself.
You don't let anyone in.
You.
I let you in.
Think about it.
What if this isn't the end?
What if it's just the beginning?
No.
They'll find us.
No. we'll keep moving.
We'll change identities. We'll...
we'll hide. They'll never catch us.
What do you say?
Uh. I say...
let's go to London.
Yeah? Madrid. Tunisia.
There are sexy places to hide.
Hey. I've never been further north
than 116th Street. so...
Because you love New York.
And I'd give my life for it. but...
there's one thing in this world
that makes me feel more alive.
And that's you.
I'm the Black Sky. Matthew.
Yeah. and I'm the
Devil of Hell's Kitchen.
The airport's just a cab fare away.
All we gotta do is survive whatever's
waiting for us behind that door.
Let's get out of here.
Remember they're
trying to kill me. not you.
Over my dead body.
No one...
escapes destiny.
You belong to us.
And you... belong in the ground.
You're done. Nobu.
Your army will crumble.
And you will leave my city alone.
Your city belongs to no one.
And she...
belongs to us!
No.
No. Elektra.
They have nothing now.
I took it all away.
It's okay. It's okay. Try not to talk.
I know... I know now...
what it feels...
to be good.
Just relax.
Try not to... try not to talk.
Does it always hurt
that much?
Yeah.
Yeah. it. uh... it
always hurts that much.
This is not the end.
Finish him.
Get down. Get down.
Don't move! Everybody get down!
Frank.
See you around. Red.
And this time. you piece of shit...
stay down.
I wanted to
say a few words. but...
I don't have any.
God rest her soul.
That should be enough.
You know. once in
college. I brought her roses.
She hates roses.
You wanted her dead.
Was it worth it?
What?
Loving her.
You taught me to cut all
my ties to humanity...
to other people.
I had only a few moments with her...
amidst all the...
noise. chaos. and the violence.
We were together only
for moments. That was all.
Orchids.
She likes orchids.
And. yeah. Stick... it was worth it.
Matt. you are the toughest son
of a bitch I have ever met.
Let's go home.
Are you gonna be okay?
I came to New York thinking
there's no way
I could feel lonely
in a city of millions.
But you do.
Somehow it makes it all worse.
I used to love coming here...
with you and Matt.
Josie's actually felt like home.
A home with... very sticky floors
and belligerent drunks. nightly.
Right.
And now. no Matt.
No us.
No Nelson. Murdock. Page.
We may not be working
together anymore...
but you're not alone. Karen.
I'm still your friend...
if you'll let me be.
Yeah. you're not getting
out that easy. Nelson.
You are stuck with me.
Wouldn't have it any other way.
You're gonna be all right.
More than all right.
- You're gonna come out on top.
-  Thanks.
How about you?
Big job. hotshot. corner
office lawyer man.
It could be exciting.
- Yeah. you could be rich.
- Yeah. rich enough to stop drinking
the rotgut swill they serve here.
Hey. Josie.
About that long-running
Nelson-Murdock tab...
- Yeah. yeah. I'll add it on.
-  No.
We're. uh... we're gonna settle up.
Close us out. Josie. We're done here.
Karen Page. what the
hell are you still doing here?
It's Christmas Eve.
Shouldn't you be home celebrating
with all that family that you...
can't stand. like everybody else?
Oh. no. I'm sorry. I must be projecting.
I. uh...
can't seem to stop staring
at a blank screen.
- Writer's block.
- Mmm.
There's a cure.
- Scotch.
- That helps you write?
Wow! No.
No. it just... helps
me not care so much.
Yeah. well. that's
definitely my problem.
I care. probably too
much. about all of it.
I don't even know if I
should start with...
the hostage crisis. or
Frank. or vigilante justice...
That's just... that's just garbage.
- Well. it's news.
- No. it's not.
Not anymore. I mean. all the facts
about that have been reported already.
Look.
If you... if you really
wanna torture yourself this holiday.
go ahead. be my guest.
But at least write something new.
Something different.
- Something that only you can write.
- Right. Which...
which would be what?
The truth.
Your truth. Karen.
All of it. Everything
that you've been through.
Don't pull any punches.
This is New York.
People think that
they've seen everything.
Prove 'em wrong. Tell them
something they don't know.
Hell. I'd
read the shit out of that.
Happy Hanukkah.
- Scotch.
- Mmm. you know. just... just in case.
I'll expect 2.000 words in my
inbox before Santa shows up.
You got it. boss.
Okay.
"What is it. to be a hero?
Look in the mirror and you'll know."
"Look into your own eyes and
tell me you are not heroic.
that you have not
endured. or suffered...
or lost the things you care about most.
And yet. here you are...
a survivor of Hell's Kitchen...
the hottest place anyone's ever known.
A place where cowards don't last long.
So... you must be a hero.
We all are.
Some more than
others. but none of us alone.
Some bloody their fists trying
to keep the Kitchen safe.
Others bloody the streets
in the hope they can stop the tide.
the crime. the cruelty...
the disregard for human
life all around them.
But this is Hell's Kitchen.
Angel or devil. rich or
poor. young or old. you live here.
You didn't choose this
town. It chose you.
Because a hero isn't someone
who lives above us. keeping us safe.
A hero is not a god or an idea.
A hero lives here...
on the street. among us. with us.
Always here but rarely recognized.
Look in the mirror
and see yourself for what you truly are.
You're a New Yorker.
You're a hero.
This is your Hell's Kitchen.
Welcome home."
Thanks for meeting me.
What am I doing here. Matt?
I. uh... I have something.
- No. I don't want it.
- I have something...
that I need you to see.
I'm Daredevil.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app